[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "I mean, the truth is Mitt Romney spent most of the first half of this year debating, so he should have the advantage, shouldn't he?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "the", "truth", "is", "Mitt", "Romney", "spent", "most", "of", "the", "first", "half", "of", "this", "year", "debating", ",", "so", "he", "should", "have", "the", "advantage", ",", "should", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RBS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, I expect him to do well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "expect", "him", "to", "do", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Are you setting the bar so low that we should now expect a fumble?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "setting", "the", "bar", "so", "low", "that", "we", "should", "now", "expect", "a", "fumble", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "I mean he must be exasperated, don't you think, that he's still in this thing?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "he", "must", "be", "exasperated", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "think", ",", "that", "he", "'s", "still", "in", "this", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, I want change.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "want", "change", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Very well, thank you, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "well", ",", "thank", "you", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "How does he do both?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "he", "do", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, I don't know how he does both.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "he", "does", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Ross, he's not suited to that role, apparently?", "question_tokens": ["Ross", ",", "he", "'s", "not", "suited", "to", "that", "role", ",", "apparently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Well, I -- you know, the last month hasn't been a very good one for the governor.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "you", "know", ",", "the", "last", "month", "has", "n't", "been", "a", "very", "good", "one", "for", "the", "governor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ross"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What would you be zinging President Obama?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "be", "zinging", "President", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I think -- I think this is a terrible strategy, actually, for the Romney campaign.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "this", "is", "a", "terrible", "strategy", ",", "actually", ",", "for", "the", "Romney", "campaign", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mitt Romney Mr. Phony"], "PERSON": ["Ross Douthat"]}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Final word from Charles?", "question_tokens": ["Final", "word", "from", "Charles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "I love that Ross Douthat just called Mitt Romney Mr. Phony.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "that", "Ross", "Douthat", "just", "called", "Mitt", "Romney", "Mr.", "Phony", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Charles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Has it been demonized a bit, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "been", "demonized", "a", "bit", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "How important has your faith been to you personally over the years?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "has", "your", "faith", "been", "to", "you", "personally", "over", "the", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "I am who I am because of what I believe.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "who", "I", "am", "because", "of", "what", "I", "believe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "To those who don't know anything about Mormonism or the Mormon Church, what are the biggest misconceptions?", "question_tokens": ["To", "those", "who", "do", "n't", "know", "anything", "about", "Mormonism", "or", "the", "Mormon", "Church", ",", "what", "are", "the", "biggest", "misconceptions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I guess I'm running for president now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "I", "'m", "running", "for", "president", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mormon Church"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "EX", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Are there misconceptions about the Mormon Church that annoy you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "misconceptions", "about", "the", "Mormon", "Church", "that", "annoy", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Of course there are.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "there", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "In your case twice with the same guy, right?", "question_tokens": ["In", "your", "case", "twice", "with", "the", "same", "guy", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Once, with the same guy.", "answer_tokens": ["Once", ",", "with", "the", "same", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "How's it going?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "it", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "It's properly in love.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "properly", "in", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Better second time around?", "question_tokens": ["Better", "second", "time", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Better.", "answer_tokens": ["Better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "You worked each other out?", "question_tokens": ["You", "worked", "each", "other", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Should I be getting nervous?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "I", "be", "getting", "nervous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Did you not try to get it Marie and Donny?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "not", "try", "to", "get", "it", "Marie", "and", "Donny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Well, he is older.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "is", "older", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "What has it been like working with your brother on and off for so long?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "it", "been", "like", "working", "with", "your", "brother", "on", "and", "off", "for", "so", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, that's the thing is we really didn't work together for like 28 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "thing", "is", "we", "really", "did", "n't", "work", "together", "for", "like", "28", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Just because you have basically done -- how many thousands of shows have you done yourself over the years, as a guest?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "because", "you", "have", "basically", "done", "--", "how", "many", "thousands", "of", "shows", "have", "you", "done", "yourself", "over", "the", "years", ",", "as", "a", "guest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Oh my gosh, we were laughing right before the show.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "my", "gosh", ",", "we", "were", "laughing", "right", "before", "the", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "And people are fascinating, Piers, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["And", "people", "are", "fascinating", ",", "Piers", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I think you have to have an endless curiosity to do this.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "have", "to", "have", "an", "endless", "curiosity", "to", "do", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "They did?", "question_tokens": ["They", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Do you think the great secret of show business, in the end, is longevity?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "great", "secret", "of", "show", "business", ",", "in", "the", "end", ",", "is", "longevity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Either that or you die young.", "answer_tokens": ["Either", "that", "or", "you", "die", "young", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A.", "Vegas", "L.A."]}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What do you do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I do a television show in L.A., and then I fly to Vegas and do the show there at night, then I get back on a plane and fly to L.A. for the show that day.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "a", "television", "show", "in", "L.A.", ",", "and", "then", "I", "fly", "to", "Vegas", "and", "do", "the", "show", "there", "at", "night", ",", "then", "I", "get", "back", "on", "a", "plane", "and", "fly", "to", "L.A.", "for", "the", "show", "that", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "As a European, do you fancy a bet?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "European", ",", "do", "you", "fancy", "a", "bet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Yes, I'll make a bet with you on the Ryder Cup.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'ll", "make", "a", "bet", "with", "you", "on", "the", "Ryder", "Cup", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Which one?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "That was a collective you, all of you.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "a", "collective", "you", ",", "all", "of", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Do I take it the party was long and glorious?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "take", "it", "the", "party", "was", "long", "and", "glorious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "It was a great party.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "great", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "What was it about that meeting, that speech, which seemed to have turned the fortunes round the next day?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "about", "that", "meeting", ",", "that", "speech", ",", "which", "seemed", "to", "have", "turned", "the", "fortunes", "round", "the", "next", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, it was a tough couple of days.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "a", "tough", "couple", "of", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "He must have said something that really got you going?", "question_tokens": ["He", "must", "have", "said", "something", "that", "really", "got", "you", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Jose was -- he was an amazing captain all week.", "answer_tokens": ["Jose", "was", "--", "he", "was", "an", "amazing", "captain", "all", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Were you feeling the same way?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "feeling", "the", "same", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "I think collectively as a team, we were playing in silence on the golf course.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "collectively", "as", "a", "team", ",", "we", "were", "playing", "in", "silence", "on", "the", "golf", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "How good a feeling is it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "good", "a", "feeling", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Even seeing them now, it really was one of the most remarkable comebacks I can think in any kind of sport.", "answer_tokens": ["Even", "seeing", "them", "now", ",", "it", "really", "was", "one", "of", "the", "most", "remarkable", "comebacks", "I", "can", "think", "in", "any", "kind", "of", "sport", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Was the major driving factor -- let's be honest here -- the fact that you knew I had a 100 dollar bet with President Clinton?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "the", "major", "driving", "factor", "--", "let", "'s", "be", "honest", "here", "--", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "knew", "I", "had", "a", "100", "dollar", "bet", "with", "President", "Clinton", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "POS", "VB", "JJS", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Yeah, that was it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "that", "was", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}}]